Hi and welcome to a new video here on my channel and after a long time this one
is another Swedish collar video. I know that a lot of you have been waiting for
this because I do not only have the collar itself but also the cups. I apologize
for the noise because my microphone is here today and these make some sounds
but I hope you can still understand me. For those of you who don't know Swedish
collar or what's so special about them this is a super high quality collar with
a really innovative locking mechanism because you have a magnet this is the
key the opener and then you can push up the plate and it opens and this is a
solid piece and this is solid piece together with the front plate. They make
a really high quality high craftsmanship product and it's also quite heavy
although this is the light version this is made of aluminium there's also a
stainless steel version and the bronze version so yeah I'm just opening it
again and then I'm going to put it on.
Careful with the head. There we go now it's in place and without the key I
cannot open it anymore. So a lot of you asked under my previous Swedish Cola
videos what happens if you lose the key and my advice is get a spare key and
last resort is a really strong magnet from the hardware store but really you
should not lose this. The cuffs work with the same principle I can use the same
key it's the same design as the collar you have the milled aluminium parts here
and the plate here, my version is stainless steel. And now I can put it on
and close it and push up the plate again. Okay wait I have to get rid of the key.
And now I did it! Of course it's easier if you have help obviously. Alright once
more, putting the key here and pushing the whole plate up until it clicks. Then
it slides down and you can open it. And to close it you just have to push the
plate up until it clicks. And here we go it's the full set. This just looks so
good together. And I receive messages from time to time from my viewers, from
my Instagram followers and they tell me I purchased the Swedish color even
though it's a bit expensive but everyone says it's worth the price, the quality is
outstanding and they love it. That's the feedback I got so far, I'm not lying. What I
have here is the 40 millimeter version so the smaller one because you can see the beautiful
boxes there's also a 50 millimeter version a bit wider
And mine is again black but with a bronze plate this time. So different color combination. Of
course you can get yours in a solid bronze or stainless steel or whatever combination you like.
Just have a look at the shop. I'll link everything down below. Another question I just received again.
why am I not wearing my Swedish collars more often in my videos? One simple reason
they're really loud and for this video it's okay because it's about Swedish collar but I think in
other videos it would really be too much noise. Okay I hope I could show you the new cuffs and
you like this video. If you're a fan of Swedish collar have a look at their social profiles and
And subscribe to my channel, check out my other videos and have a nice day. Bye!